<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Joe Graham</title>
    <link>https://joegraham.co/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Joe Graham</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2019 16:06:17 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://joegraham.co/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Hack The Box Write-up: Networked</title>
      <link>https://joegraham.co/posts/networked/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2019 16:06:17 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://joegraham.co/posts/networked/</guid>
      <description>Networked is a Linux box created by Guly that is rated fairly easily by the HTB community. Even though it was fairly easy, I got some good practice with command injection vulnerabilities and circumventing file verification methods.
Enumeration Let&amp;rsquo;s start by taking a look at what services are running on the box using nmap.
Starting Nmap 7.80 ( https://nmap.org ) at 2019-08-30 16:16 EDT Nmap scan report for 10.10.10.146 Host is up (0.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hack The Box Write-up: Bastion</title>
      <link>https://joegraham.co/posts/bastion/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2019 17:31:48 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://joegraham.co/posts/bastion/</guid>
      <description>This is my first in a series of write-ups on systems I&amp;rsquo;ve successfully exploited on HackTheBox. Bastion is a Windows host that at the time of writing has been rated fairly easy by other hackers, which was my experience as well. However, this system was still a fun system to exploit with a novel way of getting user access.
Enumeration First things first, let&amp;rsquo;s nmap the box to see what services the box has running.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1576: PAN-OS Command Injection/Shell Escape</title>
      <link>https://joegraham.co/posts/cve_2019_1576/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2019 17:15:07 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://joegraham.co/posts/cve_2019_1576/</guid>
      <description>Earlier this year I was helping RIT&amp;rsquo;s Collegiate Cyber Defense Competition (CCDC) team prepare to compete at the national competition by looking into possible attack vectors that the red team would be using to exploit the team&amp;rsquo;s infrastructure and how to defend against those attacks. Nick O&amp;rsquo;Brien and I decided to look into the Palo Alto Networks virtual firewall product to find potential pain points for the team, as PAN has been a sponsor for the competition for the last few years and has frequently provided equipment and VMs to teams for use during the competition.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello!</title>
      <link>https://joegraham.co/posts/first/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2019 11:09:28 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://joegraham.co/posts/first/</guid>
      <description>Hello! My name is Joe Graham, and welcome to my blog! I am a cybersecurity professional who specializes in penetration testing and offensive security. I plan to include things like HackTheBox write-ups and posts about penetration testing or participating in bug bounties/vulnerability disclosure. Thanks for visiting!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
